<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ihome</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="open">Open navegation Drawer</string>
    <string name="close">Close navegation Drawer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_homee">HomeeActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_favourite">Favourite</string>
    <string name="menu_account">Account</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditions">This usage policy is valid from March 2023 onwards. TERMS AND CONDITIONS - ihome ihome, a private legal entity, describes through this document the rules for using the ihome.com website and any other website, store, or application operated by the owner. By browsing this website, we consider that you agree to the terms of use listed below. If you do not agree to the terms of this agreement, please do not use this website, let alone register or submit your personal data. If we change our terms of use, we will publish the new text on this website, with an updated review date. We may modify this document at any time. If there is a significant change in the terms of this agreement, we may notify you using the contact information we have in our database or through a notification. The use of this website after the changes means that you accept the revised terms of use. If, after reading the revised version, you do not agree with its terms, please terminate your access. Section 1 - User The use of this website automatically grants you the status of User and implies your full acceptance of all guidelines and conditions included in these Terms. Section 2 - Adherence along with the privacy policy The use of this website implies adherence to these Terms of Use and the most updated version of the ihome Privacy Policy. Section 3 - Access conditions In general, access to the ihome website is free and does not require prior registration. However, to use some features, the user may need to register, creating a user account with a username and password. It is the responsibility of the user to provide only correct, authentic, valid, complete, and up-to-date information, as well as not to disclose their username and password to third parties. Some parts of this website offer the user the option to post comments in certain areas. ihome does not allow the publication of discriminatory, offensive, or illegal content, or content that infringes on copyright or any other third-party rights. The publication of any content by the user of this website, including messages and comments, implies a non-exclusive, irrevocable, and irreversible license for its use, reproduction, and publication by ihome on its website, internet platforms and applications, or even on other platforms, without any restriction or limitation. Section 4 - Cookies Information about your use of this website may be collected through cookies. Cookies are pieces of information that are stored directly on the computer you are using. Cookies allow you to collect information such as the type of browser, the time spent on the website, the pages visited, language preferences, and other anonymous traffic data. We and our service providers use the information for security protection, to facilitate navigation, display information more efficiently, and personalize your experience using this website, as well as for online tracking. We also collect statistical information about the use of the website to continuously improve our design and functionality, understand how the website is used, and help you resolve relevant issues. If you do not want your information to be collected through cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to automatically reject cookies or gives you the option to accept or reject the transfer of a specific cookie (or several) from a particular website to your computer. However, this may create inconveniences in your use of the website. The setting you choose may affect your browsing experience and the functionality that requires the use of cookies. In this regard, we reject any responsibility for the consequences arising from the limited operation of this website caused by disabling cookies on your device (inability to establish or read a cookie). Section 5 - Intellectual property All elements of ihome are the intellectual property of ihome or its licensors. These terms or the use of the website do not grant you any</string>
    <string name="room">Room type</string>
    <string-array name="room_type">
<!--        drop down items-->
        <item>Bed Room</item>
        <item>Living Room</item>
        <item>Kitchen</item>
        <item>Garage</item>
        <item>Home Outside</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>